{
    "subject": "resource/Sandy_Mart\u00ednez",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "Baseball player",
    "human_readable": "Sandy Mart\u00ednez is a Baseball player.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9415125846862793,
            "question": "Is Sandy Mart\u00ednez a professional athlete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8962634205818176,
            "question": "For which team(s) has Sandy Mart\u00ednez played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8099932074546814,
            "question": "What sport does Sandy Mart\u00ednez play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7935470938682556,
            "question": "How long has Sandy Mart\u00ednez been playing baseball?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7793790698051453,
            "question": "What position does Sandy Mart\u00ednez play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7458776235580444,
            "question": "Where is Sandy Mart\u00ednez from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7246119976043701,
            "question": "Has Sandy Mart\u00ednez won any awards in baseball?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6259433627128601,
            "question": "What are some of Sandy Mart\u00ednez's biggest accomplishments in baseball?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5172152519226074,
            "question": "What is Sandy Mart\u00ednez's batting average?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5008059144020081,
            "question": "Is Sandy Mart\u00ednez known for any particular skills or strengths?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sandy Mart\u00ednez is a Baseball player.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1086_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Sandy Mart\u00ednez's batting average?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1086_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Sandy Mart\u00ednez's biggest accomplishments in baseball?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1086_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Sandy Mart\u00ednez won any awards in baseball?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1086_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1086_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1086_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1086_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1086_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1086_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1086_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1086_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1086_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1086_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1086_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that the triple \"Sandy Mart\u00ednez is a Baseball player\" is indeed supported by the documents.\n\nHere's the structured JSON format response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Sandy Martinez was an MLB backup catcher for eight seasons and played with the Cleveland Indians (among other teams). This information supports the statement that \"Sandy Mart\u00ednez is a Baseball player.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}